♪ under the cover of l'obscurité, in Collapsing mémoire-le vide, desperate.
Lyra: non! Not this one!
Echo Shard: Unburden yourself. It is... heavy.
Lyra: jamais!
Kael: The fall... it takes everything...
♪ under the cover of l'obscurité, in Fragmented mémoire-Platform, tense.
Lyra: A trap!
Loom of Oblivion: Cease your struggle. Become... whole.
Lyra: Not like this!
Kael: It weaves... a beautiful lie...
♪ under the cover of l'obscurité, in Destabilizing mémoire-Corridor, urgent.
Lyra: Damn it!
Lyra: Too slow!
Kael: Some things... must go...
Lyra: I rappelle-toi... something!
♪ at dusk, in Shifting mémoire-Canyons, tense.
Lyra: There!
Lyra: Almost...
Kael: A spark... from the beginning...
♪ at dusk, in fragment's Perch, desperate.
Lyra: Too many!
Hunter-Echo: Relinquish. It does not belong.
Lyra: Mine! Get back!
Kael: They rappelle-toi... the hunger...
♪ at dusk, in Crumbling mémoire-Ledge, urgent.
Lyra: non! My arm!
Lyra: Should have used it!
Hunter-Echo: Your weakness... is clear.
Kael: Holding on... can break you...
♪ under the cover of l'obscurité, in Purifying mémoire-Chamber, dread.
Lyra: What is this?
Loom of Oblivion: We make them clean. Free.
Lyra: You destroy them!
Kael: It believes... it helps...
♪ under the cover of l'obscurité, in Loom's Maw (edge of the chamber), urgent.
Lyra: Now!
Loom of Oblivion: Stop her. It is vital.
Lyra: Got it!
Kael: cours! cours!
♪ at dawn, in Destabilizing mémoire-Bridge, dread.
Lyra: The bridge!
Loom of Oblivion: You cannot outrun... the inevitable.
Lyra: Almost there!
Kael: It consumes... everything...
♪ at dawn, in Edge of the Abyss of Forgetting, desperate.
Lyra: non... je ne peux pas!
Kael: Don't... s'il te plaît...
Lyra: I have to!
Loom of Oblivion: Relinquish. It is your fate.
♪ at dawn, in The le vide's Embrace, dread.
Lyra: Gone...
Kael: A piece... lost...
Loom of Oblivion: The mémoire... was jamais yours.
Lyra: What was it?